巴塞罗那
求你住手
Stop, please!
我不知道他在哪里
I don't know where he is!
他是你哥哥
He's your brother.
你当然知道
Of course you do.
我...我不知道
I-- I don't know!
我不知道
I don't know.
旋紧
知道我就告诉你了
I would tell you!
我真不知道  求你了
I would tell you. Please.
我说过了...
I told you...
-我们得试一试  -是吗
- We had to try. - Did we?
他和他哥哥都没什么联系
He's not even close with his brother.
我们总得一试
We had to try.
那现在呢
So now what?
不不不
N-N-No, no, no, no...
谢谢
Thank you.
周日  周三  周四光临的顾客
购买摩卡咖啡或冰拿铁  免费试饮
我想你
-你是不是...-是  是我
- Did you, uh... - Yes. Yeah.
花了35杯最便宜的咖啡的价钱
For the rock-bottom price of 35 coffees
他才让我...摆弄他的广告牌
he let me... mess with his sign.
要是我没发现呢
What if I didn't notice?
我知道你会发现的
I knew you would.
-怀利·杜弗瑞今晚要重出厨坛  -大卫
- Wylie Dufresne is doing a pop-up thing tonight. - David...
我知道自从阿尔德饭店关门后
I just know you've been craving those pigs-in-a-blanket
-你一直想吃卷猪肉  -我说过  我...
- since Alder closed and... - I told you, I...
我有...我有职责要...
I have... I have obligations that I have...
可问题是...
Okay, but the thing is...
我疯狂地爱上了你
I'm madly in love with you.
并且除非是我疯了
And, unless I'm crazy,
我确信你对我也有相同的感觉
I'm pretty sure you feel the same way.
大卫  我们...
David, our...
我们...错过了
our timing is... is just off.
我有职责在身  我...
I-- I-- I have these responsibilities, I'm...
我在办我这辈子最大的案件
I'm working the biggest case of my life.
所以如果你解决了案子  那...
So, if you solve the case, then...
对不起
I'm sorry.
那是什么
What is that?
这是一枚非常昂贵
Oh, this is a very expensive...
非常敏感的监控设备
very sensitive surveillance device.
如果你把它贴在台灯或者某个照明设备上
If you stick it inside of a lamp or a light switch,
它能利用光热能充电
it can power itself from radial heat,
因此它可以无限续航
so it continues to broadcast indefinitely.
窃听器吗
So it's a bug?
这是件艺术品
It's a work of art.
我需要你把它放进简的安全屋
And I want it inside Jane's safe house.
不
No.
你没权利对我说"不"
You don't say no to me.
明白吗  这东西得在24小时内开始运行
See, I want this up and running inside of 24 hours,
否则我会要你好看
or you're not gonna like the tone of my voice anymore.
有什么发现
What do you got?
我们第一次把这些纹身
All right, so when we were first inputting
放进数据库时
these tattoos into the database,
我发现简的身上
I noticed there were a lot of these
到处都是这些细小而杂散的字母
really small, stray letters all over Jane's body.
它们藏身别的图样中
They were hidden in other designs,
但用的字体都一样
but they had the same font.
所以我认为可能是某个字谜
So I figured they were an anagram for something.
"一个扳手韭葱丧钟"
"A wrenchess leek knell."
"过滤跪下麋鹿鹪鹩"
"Leach kneel elks wrens."
大概有一千种组合
There's about 1,000 of them.
其他大部分都是无意义的
The rest of them are mostly just nonsense.
你刚刚说的那两个就有意义了吗
And what you just said wasn't nonsense?
我们把所有可能的组合都输入了
We inputted every possible variation.
然后其中之一有匹配
And one of them hit?
对  就在今天早上
Yep, just this morning.
阿什沃尔小溪狗场
AshwellCreekKennels.
一个名为"绕耳王牌"在线小狗论坛里
The user name for an online puppy forum
一个人的用户名
called Ruff Around the Ears.
我不明白
I don't understand.
小狗信息板
A puppy message board?
和其他纹身指向的地方
Doesn't really line up
差别有点大啊
with where the other tattoos have led.
罪犯常常在这样的网站上互通消息
Criminals coop sites like these all the time
因为能避人耳目
and communicate because they're unmonitored.
这条线索说的是什么
What was the thread about?
是一条寻狗启示下面的回复
Uh, it's in response to someone posting about a lost puppy.
绕耳王牌
"可能丢在了美国的任何地方
"Could be anywhere in the United States.
没有标签  提供线索必有重谢"
Not tagged. Massive reward for any leads."
然后阿什沃尔小溪狗场回复说
Then AshwellCreekKennels responds,
"我们有一整窝
"We have the entire litter,
但愿您在找的也在其中
hopefully the exact one you're looking for.
需要提供项圈来证明所有权"
Will need to provide collar as proof of ownership."
如果他们说的不是狗
If they're not talking about dogs,
那他们在找什么
what are they looking for?
我还在查
Still trying to figure that out.
但随着这条线索推进
But, as the thread progresses,
阿什沃尔小溪狗场建议
AshwellCreekKennels suggests
他们下午两点到史坦顿岛的一个招待屋看看
that they check out a open house in Staten Island at 2 p.m.
我们去看看  干得漂亮
Let's check it out. Nice work.
我觉得这地方已经废弃了
I think this place is abandoned.
看起来不像是个招待屋
Don't look like much of an open house to me.
枪手
Gun!
快下楼
我掩护你
威勒  楼梯
Weller, stairs!
乔纳森
Jonathan!
你杀了他
You killed him!
里德
Reade?!
这里安全了
All clear, this area!
什么情况  他们是谁
What is this? Who are they?
不知道
Don't know.
现在想问他们估计比较难了
It's pretty hard to question them now.
盲   点
第一季  第九集
上面安全
It's all clear up there.
你怎么知道他当时要下楼
How'd you know he was coming down the stairs?
我听懂她的话了
I understood what she was saying.
我觉得是保加利亚语
I think it was Bulgarian.
又会中文  又会保加利亚语
Chinese and Bulgarian.
你以前去过不少地方啊
You must have really got around.
我们进来时  她在那里
When we came in, she was over there.
从脚印来看  她在找东西
Footprint tells me she's looking for something.
什么东西
Well, what is it?
两张宴会的门票
Two tickets to a gala.
还有枚胸针
And some sort of pin.
这些人是专业的
These guys are pros.
二楼的旅行袋里有十多本假护照
We found a duffel upstairs with about a dozen passports
他们两个的都有
for each of them.
这些护照仿真程度相当高
These are the best fakes that I have ever seen.
有套护照曾用于往返巴塞罗那
One set was used to go in and out of Barcelona,
就在一周之前
about a week ago.
巴塞罗那
Barcelona?
我查出了他们
I flagged them.
因为他们往返的日期正好和
Because they entered and exited on the exact day
一位跟家人一起度假的美国游客
an American tourist was abducted and brutally tortured
遭人绑架并折磨是同一天
when he was on vacation with his family.
他叫佩里·伯恩
His name... was Perry Byrne.
你哥哥在哪里
Where's your brother?!
知道他被折磨的原因吗
Any idea why they tortured him?
他哥哥是罗伯特·伯恩
His brother... is Robert Byrne.
就是那位转做污点证人
The accountant who turned States evidence
将维克多·莫雷洛送进监狱的会计
and put Victor Morello away.
黑帮老大  绝非善类
Mob boss... not a nice guy.
屋里的那两个人枪法精湛
The people at the house are good with guns,
还携带大量假护照
and they have a lot of passports.
我觉得他们是职业杀手
I feel like they're hired assassins.
他们在找罗伯特·伯恩
They're looking for Robert Byrne.
他可能就是"遗失的小狗"
He could be the "Lost puppy."
莫雷洛因他害自己入狱  瓦解了自己的帮派
Morello wants him dead for putting him in prison
而想杀死他  但他加入了证保计划
and dismantling his entire crew, but he's in WITSEC.
证保计划
Witsec?
证人保护计划
Witness Security Program.
杀手肯定是想从"阿什沃尔小溪狗场"那里
The assassins must be trying to buy his location
买到他现今的住址
from AshwellCreekKennels.
这都是刚发生不久的事  跟纹身有什么关系
This all just happened. How is this a tattoo?
还不清楚
I don't know yet,
但我们要立刻警告美国联邦法警
but we need to alert US Marshals immediately.
艾莉
Allie.
你好  柯特
Hello, Kurt.
你现在是法警了吗
You're a marshal now?
是  我只是想换个环境
Yeah, I was looking for a change.
好久不见
Ohh, it's been a minute.
你姐和索亚还好吗  他现在几岁了
And your sister and Sawyer? How old is he now?
九岁了
He's nine.
是啊
I know.
这是简
Uh, this is-- this is Jane.
她作为顾问协助联调局
She's working with us as a consultant.
艾莉森·奈特  联邦法警
Allison Knight, US Marshals.
幸会
Nice to meet you.
我们在网上的一个论坛里发现了一段对话
We picked up chatter in an online forum
内容是一个局外人
that points to an outsider
声称自己知道罗伯特·伯恩的下落
knowing the location of Robert Byrne,
而罗伯特如今正在政府的保护之下
who we believe is under government protection.
没错
He is.
谈话中的用词让我们很担忧
What concerns us is the phrasing of the correspondence.
它暗示了发帖人
It alludes to the poster
手中有"整窝"的信息
having information on "The entire litter."
莫雷洛案的其他证人有暴露的可能吗
Could other Morello witnesses be compromised?
不只是莫雷洛的证人
Not just Morello witnesses.
事关重大  我们封锁了消息
We've been keeping this quiet for obvious reasons,
但我们的证保计划数据库被入侵了
but we had a WITSEC data breach.
你们被入侵了
You were hacked?
超过两千个证人的
Just over 2,000 witnesses
新身份与新住址都暴露了
had their new identities and locations compromised.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我们正竭尽全力
We're doing the best we can
将他们重新安置  给他们新身份
to relocate them and get them new backgrounds,
但你也能想像到  这需要花一些时间
but, as you can imagine, it's gonna take some time.
你需要立刻重新安置
You need to relocate Robert Byrne
罗伯特·伯恩以及他的家人
and his entire family, immediately.
我们正在办  但安置其他证人
We are... but it's gonna take at least six months
还至少需要半年时间
to reassign the others.
我们得找出幕后黑手
We need to find out whoever's doing this
阻止信息泄露  得赶快
and shut it down... now.
所以"整窝"的意思也许是
So "the entire litter" probably means
泄露的证保计划名单
the hacked WITSEC list.
-那就大事不妙了  -是啊
- That would be very, very bad. - Yeah.
至少我们知道
Well, at least we know
他们在哪里交易
where the the exchange is gonna happen.
就是今天下午五点的这场募款活动
At this fundraiser, today at 5 P.M.
拿着
Hold this.
我有个推论
I have a theory.
我们在行李包的暗袋里找到的这个
We found this in a hidden pocket in the duffel.
估计价值大约六百万美元
We think it might be worth as much as $6 million.
"需提供项圈作为所有权凭证"
"Will need to provide collar as proof of ownership."
项圈是购买名单的款项
The collar is payment for the list.
没错  所以...
Right, so...
卖家把门票
the seller leaves the tickets
和胸针留在屋子里
and the lapel pin in the house.
而门票用于进入交易的地点
And we know that the tickets are for the location of the hand-off.
可胸针代表什么
But what's this pin?
卖家识别买主的信物
A way to be identified by the seller.
我也这么想的
That'd be my guess.
对  因为我想这两位专业杀手可不会
Yeah, because it's not like these two professional killers
把自己的照片和外貌描述
are gonna send an email with a photo
用邮件发给对方
and a description of what they look like.
门票用来通知他们交易地点
The tickets tell them where to be,
而胸针用来识别他们的身份
and the pin identifies who they are.
但如果他们不知道买家的相貌...
But if they don't know what the buyers look like...
我们就可以卧底进去
we can go undercover.
假装成买家  抓住他们
Pose as the buyers and take 'em down.
他们知道买家是一男一女
They're expecting a man and a woman.
女的会说保加利亚语
A woman who speaks Bulgarian.
我可以扮
I can do it.
等一下
Wai-wai-wai-wait.
要是我们错了呢
What if we're wrong?
弄错了胸针的含义
About the pin,
误认为他们不知道买家的相貌
about them knowing what the buyers look like.
卧底行动很可能瞬间暴露
No, this thing could go sideways real quick.
我们必须抓住这次机会
We gotta take that chance.
简和我假扮买家
All right, Jane and I will pose as the buyers.
你们三个  装作路人
You three, work the crowd.
支援我俩  抓捕他们
Back us up. Take 'em down.
我们去换礼服吧  要去参加宴会了
Let's get dressed up. We're going to a gala.
好了  别看了
All right, all right. Enough.
看起来很帅  特别探员
Lookin' good, Special Agent.
谢谢
Thank you.
改天你该约我出去
You should take me out sometime.
是啊  上次的约会可不怎么顺利
Yeah... that didn't seem to go so well, the last time.
是的  可有些错误再犯一次也挺好
Yeah, but some mistakes are better the second time.
你知道  那些美好时光
You know... all the good times,
意料之中的约会失败
none of the surprise when it doesn't work out.
-是啊  -你觉得怎样
- Yeah. - What do you say?
我可以给爱特宝餐厅的麦克打电话
I could call Mike at Attaboy,
定我们的老位子
get our old table.
让他准备两份拉加维林威士忌
Tell him to double-stock the Lagavulin.
不行  我...
Well... No, no, I'm...
我明白了
I get it.
什么  不
What? No.
不是这样的
No.
当然
Sure.
纹身有点妨碍乔装
The, um... tattoos sort of ruin the whole undercover thing,
所以他们用粉底把它们遮住了
so they covered them with makeup.
穿这身礼服我感觉好傻
I feel ridiculous in this dress.
我不这么认为
That is not the word I would use.
注意安全
Stay safe.
别让对方离开自己的视线范围
Don't take your eyes off each other.
既然假扮夫妻  就得带上结婚戒指
Now, the couple were wearing wedding rings.
所以...
So...
对  当然了
Oh, right, yeah. Of course.
您的胸针真不错  先生
That's a wonderful pin, sir.
我能看一下您的票吗
Can I see your tickets?
请跟我来
Follow me, please.
我去开车
I'll get the car.
我们不能跟丢他们
We can't lose them.
请把你们的手机给我
I'm gonna need your cell phones.
您也知道我的老板是个极其谨慎的人
As you know, my employer is an extremely cautious man.
我们要去哪儿
Where are we going?
到了你就知道了
Why don't you wait and see?
能追踪到他们吗
Can we trace 'em?
手机上的追踪器显示他们还在轿车里
The trackers on their phones say they're still in the limo.
他们得靠自己了
They're on their own.
举起手来
Arms up!
够了
Enough.
我说够了
I said enough!
没关系  没关系
It's fine, it's fine.
拜托  让他照章办事
Please, let him do his job.
我不喜欢他对你动手动脚
I don't like him touching you.
我也不喜欢你对他动手
And I don't like you touching him.
没问题
You're good.
谢谢
Thank you.
那边请
That way.
刚才是怎么回事
What the hell was that about?
你是我老婆
You're my wife.
我不知道这是哪里
I don't know where we are.
没有枪  没后援
We have no guns, no backup--
我们要怎么抓人
How are we gonna arrest this guy?
执行新计划  拿到名单
Well, new plan: Secure the list,
活着出去
get out of here alive.
好
Okay.
他们乘坐的直升机申请了一个伪造的飞行计划
The helicopter they were on filed a bogus flight plan,
关掉了应答器
turned off its transponder,
低空飞行躲过了雷达
and stayed low enough to evade radar.
我们查不到它的去向
We have no idea where it went.
宴会的门票是用现金买的  无法追踪
They paid cash for the gala tickets-- no trace.
无论这个幕后主使是谁
Whoever is behind this
他想尽了一切办法不被人找到
has gone to extraordinary measures not to be found.
去看看论坛的其他帖子
Go over the other forum posts.
也许能找到一些线索
There might be a clue in there somewhere.
马上去办
Yeah, on it.
下午好
Good afternoon.
借一步说话
A word?
我们现在真的非常忙
We're actually extremely busy right now.
用不了多久
It'll just take a second.
刚是什么情况
What was that about?
不清楚
I have no idea.
你把格雷罗关起来了
So you have Guerrero in custody.
简的一枚纹身让威勒团队找到了他
One of Jane's tattoos led Weller and his team right to him.
别担心  我...
Don't worry, I'm...
"我正在处理"  我知道
"I'm handling it." Yeah, yeah, I know.
但这事一丝一毫都没处理
Nothing about this is handled.
我们必须立即遏制它
We need to contain this, immediately.
我准备让他签一份追溯证明
I'm having him sign a backdated confirmation
表明他是我的秘密线人
that he was my CHS.
那是远远不够的
We are way beyond that now.
给简纹身的人是冲着我们来的
Whoever did this to Jane is coming for us.
这显而易见
It's plain as day.
格雷罗必须消失
Guerrero needs to disappear.
他关在联邦监狱里  我们不能...
He's in a federal prison. We can't just...
能  我们能
Yes... we... can.
只要我们伪造一份书面记录
If we create a paper trail,
所有问题都迎刃而解了
all our problems go away.
如果有人想通过格雷罗揭发白昼计划
If someone is trying to expose Daylight through Guerrero,
让他合法化就能让他们的计划落空
making him legit neutralizes everything they think they have.
如果他不愿意合作呢
What if he doesn't cooperate?
如果他不签  我就把他扔到混合牢房去
If he doesn't sign, I'll release him into gen-pop!
称他是内奸  就是置他于死地
Brand him a rat. It's a death sentence.
他不傻  他会签的
He's not stupid. He'll sign!
你知道这是最好的选择了
This is the best option, and you know it.
好吧  走着瞧
Well, we'll see.
等着瞧
Won't we?
卡尔70岁生日快乐
一个生日聚会竟然这么多保安
Lot of security for a birthday party.
楼上也有
Top of the line, too.
你觉得我们是来见"卡尔"的吗
Do you think we're here to meet "Carl"?
我也不知道
I don't know.
现在我们要怎么做
Well... what should we do now?
我们就等着
We should wait...
直到卖家联系我们
till the seller makes contact.
在那之前...
Until then...
我们应该尽量融入这里
we should try to blend in.
不行  我...
No, I...
我觉得我不会跳舞
I don't think I can dance.
这个嘛
Well...
今天早上之前
up until this morning...
你还不会说保加利亚语呢
you couldn't speak Bulgarian.
谁知道呢
Who knows?
你也可能是个探戈冠军
You could be a tango champion.
所以...
So, um...
你和那个...联邦法警之间
You and that, um... US Marshal over here.
-是的  -你们看着很...
- Yeah. - You looked pretty...
是的  我们交往过
Yeah. We used to date.
很短一段
A little while.
多短
Well, how little?
一年左右
A year or so.
这也叫短吗
That's a little?
我们不是...
We weren't...
很擅长沟通
the best at communicating.
我都不知...
Well, I don't even...
那你以前结过婚吗
Have you... ever been married?
没有
No.
没结过
Never married.
我太挑剔
I'm too choosy.
我...
I, um...
我出现了一段记忆
I've been having memories
看起来我可能已经订婚了
that make it seem like I might have been engaged.
你记起什么了
What'd you remember?
短暂的片段
Moments, fragments.
都感觉...
It all seemed so...
和现在的我相去甚远
far away from where I am now.
他可以见你们了
He's ready for you.
终于来了
About time.
尽管费了些功夫  但我们还是恢复了
So it took a little doing, but we were able to recover
一些"阿什沃尔小溪狗场"删掉的帖子
a bunch of deleted AshwellCreekKennels posts.
似乎他已经使用这个网站好几年了
It looks like they've been using the site for a couple of years.
这就解释了为什么它会纹在简身上
That would explain how it got onto Jane's body.
我的团队从帖子里的语言中
My team has been lining up the language in the post
推出一些很危险的事情
with some pretty serious stuff.
军火交易  大量的个人身份泄漏
Arms deals, massive personal identity breaches.
幕后人物是谁
Who's doing this?
直升机  老房子
The helicopter, the old house...
都是由空壳公司出资
they were both paid for by shell companies
以给空壳公司下属的空壳公司买的
for shell companies of shell companies.
几乎不可能知道谁拥有它们
Next to impossible to know who really owns them.
-但是...-它们的会计师相同
- But... - They have the same accountant.
他尽力掩盖自己的行迹
He did his best to cover his tracks,
但所有的线索追溯到
but all roads lead back to...
雷尼尔·艾伯赛  注册会计师
Rainier Abosay, CPA.
把他带过来吧  看看他为谁工作
So let's bring him in, see who he works for.
问题就在这里
That's the thing.
他只为一个人做事
He only works for one man.
而那个人是世界上最危险的人之一
And he's one of the most dangerous guys in the world.
这是最棒的部分  终于来了
That's the best part of it. There they are!
我的天啊  有生之年
Oh, my goodness, as I live and breathe,
终于见到你们了
there they are.
瑞奇·多特康
Rich Dotcom.
真高兴你们能来
So glad you could make it.
实在太高兴了
So glad indeed.
你们去见过卡尔了吗
Wow. Did you guys see Carl?
-跟他说生日快乐了吗  -没有
- Did you wish him a happy birthday? - No.
今天其实并非真是他七十岁生日
He's not actually 70 today, by the way, yeah.
我们只是跟他闹着玩的
We just did that to mess with him.
不过他确实老了  挺显老的
He is old, though. He's pretty old-looking.
我觉得他可能病了
I think he might be sick.
非常感谢  酒别停啊
Thank you very much. Keep those comin'.
不用了  谢谢
No thanks.
很抱歉麻烦你们
And, uh, I'm sorry to have to put you
让你们来这里一趟
through all this hassle. To get up here.
你们知道的  我得小心行事
You know, I gotta play it safe.
还有
Um, hello.
不用我说你们也知道
I don't have to tell you.
我竟然跟两位真正的杀手在聊天
I'm talking to two real-life, actual assassins.
对吧  我是说...
Right? I mean...
我得说  我真觉得太激动了
I gotta tell you, this is very exciting for me.
他们搜过你们身了吗
Mm! Did they pat you down?
当然也没什么区别  因为我知道
Not that that matters, 'cause I'm sure you could
你们估计拿个勺子都能杀人
probably kill somebody with a spoon.
见鬼  你们可能连勺子都不用吧
Heck, you probably don't even need the spoon.
太厉害了
So bad-ass.
不好意思  你说你叫...
I-I'm sorry, you said your name was...
瑞奇·多特康[土豪.com]
Rich Dotcom?
对  我妈非常喜欢互联网
Yeah, my mom was a big fan of the Internet.
开个玩笑
That's a joke.
你们俩的幽默感还真跟我想的一样
You guys are about as funny as I thought you'd be.
来吧
Come on!
原名戈德·恩维尔
Born Gord Enver.
戈德·恩维尔
很厉害的程序员
Pretty decent programmer.
居无定所  做有偿技术服务
Knocked around, made a reasonable living
过得还不错
as a tech mercenary.
但问题是
But here's the thing.
他是世界上最早意识到
He was one of the first guys in the world
比特币有巨大前景的人之一
to realize that the Bitcoin was gonna be a big deal.
他把一切都投进去
Put everything he had into it,
没过几年  他就有五亿身价了
and within a couple years, he was worth $1/2 billion.
聪明人
Smart guy.
在那之后
After that,
他改名为瑞奇·多特康
he changed his name to Rich Dotcom.
瑞奇·多特康
-当我没说  -让我猜猜
- I take it back. - Let me guess.
他拿着这些钱
He took all that money
去世界各地做了很多好事吧
and did a whole bunch of good in the world with it?
正好相反
Oh, opposite, opposite.
他成为了暗网里最有信誉的人之一
He became one of the most trusted names on the Dark Net.
无论什么东西  只要你有钱
Anything you need, if you have the money,
722号小站
瑞奇·多特康都能替你搞到
Rich Dotcom can get it for you.
那他是黑客吗
So he's a hacker?
他曾经是黑客  现在嘛...
He was a hacker. Now he's just...
他变得坏多了
He's a lot, lot worse.
同志们  我要用下这间房
Hey, fellas, I'm gonna need the room.
瑞奇  求你了  对不起
Rich, please. I'm sorry.
好的  我也很抱歉
Yeah, I'd be sorry, too.
等他们掏出真家伙的时候
Hey, wait till they get the pipes out.
那场面就不好看了
That's gonna suck.
他们得再检查一遍你们俩
Hey, they gotta do one more pass on you guys,
防止你们把这里偷录下来
just to make sure you're not recording the whole thing.
你没问题了  请站过去
You're clear. Step over there, please.
摩纳哥那次任务  是你们做的吧
So the Monaco job, that was you guys, right?
那家伙一直以来都是我的眼中钉
Wow, I mean, that guy was a thorn in my side for so long,
很高兴终于有人让他闭嘴了
I'm glad someone finally "Fffuh."
不过是谁动的手呢  是...
Who did it, though? Was it...
我是说  是谁割了他的喉咙
I mean, who actually slit his throat?
是我
I did.
用我的蝴蝶刀
With my butterfly knife.
说实话
I gotta be honest,
你现在的样子
this whole thing that you got going on right now
真的引起了我的兴趣
is really working for me.
你跟那个固执男是什么情况
I mean, what's the deal with you and Stubbles over there?
你们是开放的关系
Are you guys fully... open,
还是对彼此忠诚
or is it a committed thing?
如果是后者的话...
'Cause if it's the latter, I mean...
我就在旁边看看也行
I'm okay to just watch, you know?
我最近突然发现
It's something that I've discovered
自己挺喜欢干这种事的
I actually really like doing.
我也不知道是怎么回事
I don't know where it comes from,
但那真的会勾起我的性趣
but it really turns me on, you know?
就当是这次旅程的一部分好了
It's just sort of part of this journey, so...
你觉得他会同意吗
Do you think he'd be cool with that?
你觉得他会接受这种事吗
Do you think he'd be open to that sort of thing?
你觉得他是个开放的人吗
Do you think he's an open person?
可以谈正事了吗
We doing this or what?
你喜欢会吃醋的类型啊
什么类型我都喜欢
可以把项链给我了吗
Okay, may I have the necklace, please?
我这里有个哈西德派的家伙
I got this Hasidic guy on the premises.
他是个真正的派对狂人
He's a real party animal.
他一会儿会检验项链的真伪
And, uh, he's gonna check out the necklace
每颗钻石都要查  所以需要点时间
stone by stone, which is gonna take a while.
但为表诚意
But, in good faith,
我会先把名单给你们
I'm gonna give you the list.
不过...你们还不能离开这里
Now... you just can't leave the party
得等我们确认项链是真的
until the necklace checks out.
如果不是的话  你们俩都得死
And, if it doesn't you're both dead.
我开玩笑的  又或者不是
I'm kidding. Or am I?
有时我自己都搞不清
Sometimes, I don't even know.
我得拿回这个
Oh, I'm gonna need this.
还有一枚胸针
Another pin?
这是另一位买家的
It's another buyer.
我以为名单只卖给了我们
I thought that we had the only copy.
才卖六百万吗
For $6 million?
别自以为是了  哥们儿
Get over yourself, man.
你知道我们费了多大劲
Do you know how hard it was
才得到这份名单吗
to acquire this list?
你买的是使用权  不是所有权
You paid for access, not exclusivity.
你们担心什么  担心他们会
What are you worried about, that they're gonna
抢先一步杀了你们想杀的人吗
kill the guys you wanna kill first?
-别这么幼稚  -还有多少买家
- Don't be childish. - How many other buyers?
只有你俩了
Just the two of you.
暂且是
For now.
听着  一旦确认项链是真的
Look... once the stones check out,
你们就可以坐上直升机
you get to go on a helicopter
然后想去哪就去哪
and go wherever you wanna go.
但在此期间
But, in the meantime,
我在楼下准备了价值十万美元的鱼子酱
I got $100,000 worth of caviar downstairs,
还有年份在一战以前的美酒
and some wine that's older than the First World War.
那么...玩得开心点
So... enjoy yourselves.
尤其是你
This guy in particular.
看看你那愁眉苦脸的样子
Look at that stern mug on your face.
放轻松点  哥们儿
You need to let loose, man!
大周五晚上的  扯开嗓子狂欢吧
I mean, it's Friday night, for cryin' out loud.
今天周二
It's Tuesday.
好吧  有些地方已经周五了
Well, it's Friday somewhere.
这里已经有人拿到名单了
Someone else here already has the list.
我们得把另一个U盘拿回来
We gotta get the other USB drive back.
我们该怎么找到另一个买家
How are we gonna find the other buyer?
胸针是唯一能识别买家的信物
Their only identifying feature is the pin
可如今也已经不在他们身上了
they're no longer wearing.
如果能侵入安保系统的话...
Well, if we can get into the security system...
我们可以查监控
we can go through the footage.
看看在瑞奇收回之前
Find out who was wearing that pin
是谁戴着那枚胸针
before Rich took it back.
我的天啊  瞧瞧你们
Oh, my Goodness, look at you.
见到你们真好
So good to see you.
刚刚在楼上  他把你带去旁边
What did he say to you upstairs,
都说了些什么
when I was out of earshot?
我觉得他是想睡我
I think he wants to sleep with me.
或是睡我们
Or us.
我没太明白
It was hard to tell.
太好了
Perfect.
一杯波本  一杯马提尼  谢谢
Bourbon and a martini, please.
你在打我老婆的主意吗
You propositioned my wife?
什么
What?
你在打我老婆的主意吗
Did you proposition my wife?
打主意  你把这事说得
Proposition? That makes it sound
-真下流  -放开
- very seedy. - Get off!
放开他
Boys!
其实...我也邀请你了
Now... You were also invited.
我对你也很感性趣的
I'm kinda sweet on you as well.
没搞错吧
Really?
放轻松  去吃点墨西哥辣椒卷
Relax. Have some jalapeno poppers.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是在干什么
What was that about?
为了这个
About this.
你打我老婆的主意吗
You propositioned my wife?
你在打我老婆的主意吗
Did you proposition my wife?
打主意  放开他
Proposition? Boys!
不是只有你才有隐藏技能
You're not the only one with hidden talents.
干杯
Cheers.
不是吧
You kidding me?
这里拨不了外线
I can't get an outside line.
你能找到前门的监控吗
Can you isolate the camera above the front door?
可以
Yep.
快  快啊
Come on, come on.
来吧
Come on...
这里
Oh, there.
他一个人来的吗
Did he walk in alone?
对  看起来是的
Yeah, it looks that way.
好吧  你起来
All right, hop up.
我删掉监控录像
I'm gonna wipe this computer.
不行  你删了的话
No, if you wipe it,
他们就会知道有人来过
they'll know someone was in here.
如果不删  他们就会知道是我们
And if I don't, they'll know it was us.
我们要采取行动了
We're about to make some moves.
不能让他们发现
We don't want them to see.
-有收获吗  -在直升机飞行半径内
- Got something? - We've been searching properties
我们搜寻了恩维尔拥有的房产
that Enver owns within a helicopter's flying radius.
你是说多特康吧
Don't you mean Dotcom?
我不会叫他多特康的
I'm not calling him Dotcom.
找到了吗
Any hits?
-有七处  -这么多
- Seven. - That's a lot.
有些在市内
Some are in the city,
但我想可以排除
but I think we can rule those out.
这五个区里  没多少地方
Not a lot of places to land a helicopter
能停得下直升机的
within the five boroughs.
派探员去查实
Send agents to be sure.
其它房产都在东海岸附近
The other properties are up and down the East Coast.
开架直升机
Take a helicopter
过去逐一排查
and check them out, one by one.
我们会找回他们的
We'll get 'em back.
是  长官
Yes, ma'am.
另一位买家在那
There's the other buyer.
你打算怎么办
Okay, how do you wanna play it?
把他单独引开  然后拿下
Gotta get him alone and take him down.
不等我们的项链检查完可以走时
Shouldn't we wait until our necklace clears
再动手吗
and we can leave?
我们不知道他什么时候会走
We have no idea when he's going to leave.
现在就得行动
We have to act now.
好
Okay.
怎么才能把他单独引开呢
How do we get him alone?
利用我们的共同点
Use the one thing we have in common.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
-我认识你吗  -不认识
- Do I know you? - No.
我也不认识你
And I don't know you.
但我想我们都刚到手一件东西
But I think we both just got had.
什么意思
Excuse me?
那份名单
The list.
他说过我们能得到完整的
He told us we'd get the complete
证保计划名单
WITSEC list.
但他只给了我们一半
He only gave us half.
我相信他也骗了你吧
I'm pretty sure he lied to you as well.
我们有一台电脑
We have access to a computer,
如果愿意  你可以自己去查
if you'd like to check for yourself.
我可是付了三百万的
If I paid $3 million,
我要得到完整的名单
I'd want the whole thing.
-你付了三百万吗  -对
- You paid three? - Yeah.
我给了九百万
I paid nine.
你有电脑吗
You have a computer?
对
Yes.
带路吧
Lead the way.
没问题
Of course.
U盘在哪
Where's the USB?
电脑在哪
Where's the computer?
把U盘交出来
Give me the drive.
快帮我找U盘
Help me find the drive.
还说你俩对3P没兴趣
And you guys said you weren't into threesomes.
好了  那谁打算编个瞎话
Okay, now, who wants to lie to me
骗我这里到底发生了什么
about what the hell is going on down here?
本想给我好朋友卡尔办场有趣的派对
Try to throw a fun party for my best friend Carl,
然后就听说有人闯进我办公室
and then I hear somebody's broken into my office
弄坏了一个很贵的荷兰监控系统
and destroyed a very expensive Dutch surveillance system.
接着就看到我最爱的一对在这里
Then I see my favorite couple down here
和我一位重要客户抓屁股玩
playing grab-ass with a valued customer.
得承认  我有点不高兴了
I gotta admit I'm a little upset.
有人想说两句吗  因为没有的话
Is someone gonna start talking, because otherwise,
我就要开始胡思乱想了
my imagination is gonna start to go.
而且我这人还有点胆小加偏执
And I tend to err on the side of scary and paranoid.
他是联调局的
He's a Fed.
不会  他通过安检了
No, he checked out.
我们都通过了
We all checked out.
说说  他怎么就是联调局的呢
Okay, what makes him a Fed?
他找上我们...
He came up to us...
张口就说名单的事
and started talking about the list.
他是怎么知道的
So how would he know about that?
因为他是另一位买家
He's the other buyer?
我要是你  我就得担心了
Then I'd be real worried if I were you,
因为你把偷来的名单
because you just sold that list
卖给了它原来的主人
to the same people you stole it from.
搜他身
Search him.
这是我的安全卡
He's got my security card.
能把你的枪给我吗
Can I have your gun, please?
你俩喜欢法国白兰地吗
Hey, would you two care for a cognac?
一片漆黑
The lights are out.
红外扫描没发现有人
No heat signatures.
这里没什么异常
Okay, there's nothing going on over here.
去下一家
Move on to the next one.
知道吗  我买这瓶白兰地
You know, I purchased this cognac
可花了十万英镑啊
for 100,000 British pounds sterling.
佩服
Impressive.
举杯吧
Shall we?
你们先请
Please, after you.
这么好的酒怎能不分享呢
It's too good not to share, right?
你们常喝白兰地吗
You guys big cognac drinkers?
并不是
Not really.
当首次提取葡萄汁时
See, the first time they distill the grapes,
提取出来的酒简直没法喝
it comes out as this basically undrinkable wine.
酒精含量也只有7%到9%
And it's only about seven or nine percent alcohol.
简直是在做无用功
It's basically a waste of time.
这酒拿出来就是耻辱
Should be ashamed of itself.
但是再提取一次
But then, they distill it again,
酒精含量就达到了70%
and it clocks in at about 70 percent.
而且...非常纯净
And it's just... crystal clear.
他们称其为"白兰地"[生命之水]
Eau-de-vie, they call it.
是法语
It's French.
所以你得提纯两次
But you gotta distill it twice.
摩纳哥那次任务是你俩共同完成的  对吗
So you guys did the Monaco job together, right?
我已经说过...
I already told...
我在跟怒汉先生说话呢
I'm talking to Angry over here.
你别看她
Don't look at her.
我就是问你个问题
I'm just asking you a question.
摩纳哥那次任务是你俩共同完成的  对吗
You guys did the Monaco job together, right?
是的
Yeah.
那太好了
That's great.
我讨厌那家伙
You know, I hated that guy.
他就是个爱发牢骚  哭哭啼啼的人
He was such a whiny, sniveling little...
是谁动的手呢  是谁动手...
Who did it, though? Who actually...
杀掉他的
put him down?
别...看她
Don't... look at her.
是她
She did.
对  当然是她干的
Right... of course she did.
对吗  当然是她
Right? Course she did.
看看她
I mean, look at her.
天啊  你也能杀死我
Jeez, you could put me down, too.
怎么杀的
How?
对  没错
Yeah, that's right.
怎么杀的
How?
你说得对
You are right.
如此美好...
This is too good...
怎能不分享
not to share.
对吗
Right?
动作真快
That was fast.
离开桌子
Move away from the desk.
真是越来越令人激动了  对吗
Okay, this just got really exciting, didn't it?
把另一个U盘给我
Give me the other USB key.
否则呢
Or what?
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
好  怒汉先生  拿去吧
Okay, Angry, here we go.
是给你还是...
Is it for you or...
-给我  -好
- Give it to me! - Okay.
好了
All right.
我们一起走出去
We're gonna walk outside.
你让直升机回来
You're gonna bring back the chopper.
我们三个
And the three of us
一起回城里去
are gonna head back to the city.
是吗
We are?
好
Oh. Okay.
你不按我说的做...
You step out of line...
我就毙了你
I will kill you.
明白吗
You understand?
明白  听上去相当简单明了
Yeah, that seems pretty straightforward.
很好
Good.
快走
Now... move.
你让他们把直升机叫回来
I want you to ask these two to bring back the chopper.
懂了
Gotcha.
伙计们  今晚真疯狂
Hey, guys! Crazy night tonight.
你们能不能帮个忙  帮我杀了他们
Um, can you do me a favor and kill these two, please?
我现在不应该已经死了吗
Hey, shouldn't I be dead already?
好吧  你们是警察
Yeah, OK, you're cops.
是联调局的吧
Feds, right?
如果你们是雇佣军
Yeah, if you were mercenaries,
就不会费心夺走第二份名单了
you wouldn't have bothered to recover the second list.
我说的没错吧
I'm right, aren't I?
对啊
Yeah.
还有  警察不会射杀
And, see, cops don't shoot the suspects
他们抓住的嫌疑犯  那样是违法的
they have in custody... it's against the law.
既然我的手下都掏出枪了
So, now that my men have their guns out,
不如你们把枪放下
why don't you put yours down
我们今晚就到此为止
and we can call it a night?
或者你杀了我  然后他们杀了你们
Or you could kill me, and then they'll kill you.
你们肯定算得清利害得失
I'm sure you've done the math on that.
或者会这样
Or there's that.
快跑  进池边小屋
Come on! In the pool house!
快跑
Come on, run!
到柱子后面去
Get behind the post!
躲在柱子后面
Stay behind that pillar!
我没子弹了
I'm out!
他们在那
Right there!
我们得解决掉守卫
We gotta take out those guards.
联调局
It's the FBI!
你们被包围了
You are surrounded!
放下武器
Put down your weapons!
我们是联调局的
We are the FBI.
你被捕了
You are under arrest.
今天干得好
Nice work today.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的燕尾服呢
Where's the tux?
我可等不及脱下它
I couldn't wait to get out of that thing.
之前答应喝一杯呢
So how 'bout that drink?
去不了了
I can't.
我们今晚要庆祝简的乔迁之喜
We have a housewarming thing tonight, for Jane.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你追回名单
Thanks for getting that list back.
我很高兴能帮上忙
Oh, glad I could help.
他有几堵心墙  从不对人敞开
He's got a few walls that may never come down...
他可能是我见过最内向的人
and is maybe the most introverted person I've ever met,
但除此之外  你再也找不到比他更好的人
but aside from that, you won't find a better man.
我们是不是该把戒指摘下来了
We should probably take those rings off.
对
Oh, right.
你不必那样做
You don't have to do that.
不  我必须
Yes... I do.
索尔·格雷罗
我受雇于宝芬妮·梅菲尔  是一名联调局线人
新消息  任务完成